Please take care in the sweltering heat!
Pocheon, Gyeonggi Province, Summer in Korea
Hello, I'm Ryu
On a summer day when the daytime temperature is over 35℃, I came out camping with Ryua
I came to a place with a dense shade of trees, but it's inevitably hot
I'm going to hurry up and set up a tent to block the hot sun
Today's tent has a double-sided pigment coating, so it has a high UV protection rate
It's a simple structure, so you can install it quickly
It can open all sides, so you can use it like a tarp
I thought it would be good to use on a summer day like today, so I brought it
Since I made shade with a tent, I'll make a space for Ryua to rest
Ryua is here!!
Ryua can't be hot, so I'll quickly install the air conditioner
Air conditioning temperature set to 17℃!
Maybe because the air conditioner is cool, Ryua is starting to doze off
Now that I've made space for her, I'll set up the equipment one by one
To keep it cold, I divided the drinks and ingredients into two coolers
I put water and ice in a water jug to make sure I'm hydrated
Now that there are a lot of flying insects and mosquitoes, I quickly smoked mosquito scents
I prepared extra clothes so that I could change my sweaty clothes
I also brought a circulator to make my day colder today
We're all ready to spend the day here
Then we'll slowly enjoy this hot summer day
Now that I'm ready, I'm going to enjoy a cool lunch
(Water)
(Noodles)
(Cucumber)
(Stir-fried sesame seeds)
(Cherry tomato)
(Apples)
I prepared an apple for Ryua's lunch snack today
(Ice)
(Beans water)
I need to get something out of the car to enjoy my cold lunch
There's no valley here. I thought it would be hot in the afternoon, so I prepared it
I'm going to dip my feet in a tube full of water and ice and eat noodles
(Chonggak kimchi / Young radish kimchi)
Wow!
(Makgeolli / Korea rice wine)
I'm going to dip my feet in water so that Ryua can cool off
Now that I've dipped my feet in the water, I'll start eating the soybean noodles
(Bye...)
Come here!
Yes, stay there
Oh, my!
I guess Ryua likes air conditioning more than cold water
Cold soybean noodles on a hot summer day are delicious
The combination of cold bean noodles and Chonggak kimchi went really well together
Ryua eats apples well to see if they taste good
We enjoyed this cool lunch
a languid afternoon
I'm going to spend time reading a book
Small questions about the dog's heart "My dog's mind counseling center"
There's a book where you can find out the dog's mind at the bookstore by chance
I bought it to read it out of curiosity
I thought I could understand how she feels if I read the book
Oh!
I was reading a book and I saw something I was always curious about
Q. Why does a dog roll around on the floor because it's itchy?
Maybe, but there's probably another reason!
I guess the reason Ryua rolls around is because she feels good
While I was reading, the sun started to set
We're going to change and go for a walk nearby
I went out for a walk with Ryua to a nearby reservoir before sunset
The sun is setting. The temperature is dropping. It's a good temperature for a walk
And it's good to hear the sound of frogs and grass bugs while walking
I went out for a walk at sunset for the first time here
Maybe because of the lighting, the atmosphere and day are very different
We went for a walk in a good mood
(Chicken feet)
(Seasoning place)
(Water)
I'm going to make spicy chicken feet for dinner tonight
I'll wait until the sauce boils down
(Cheongyang red pepper)
(Red pepper)
(Rice)
(Sesame oil)
(Kim /Laver)
(Rice ball)
(Egg)
(Water)
(Powder seasoning)
(Steamed eggs)
(Sesame oil)
(Stir-fried sesame seeds)
I'm going to prepare Ryua's special food
(Beef)
(Soju / Korean distilled spirits)
No, do you chew it..
Since Ryua finished her dinner, I'll enjoy my dinner now
Chicken feet is seasoned spicy. It's delicious
Rice balls and steamed eggs that I made to eat with chicken feet
It's a perfect taste
I'm sweating like it's raining
I can't stop it because it's so addictive
We enjoyed this spicy and hot dinner
But the temperature dropped a lot at night
But maybe because there are a lot of trees here, there are a lot of bugs
I don't think it's going to be easy to sleep, so I'll set up a coat tent and sleep
I'm ready to sleep if you change the air conditioner
Ryua fell asleep alone in the meantime
(French pie / Snacks)
I'm going to watch a program that I enjoy and go to sleep
Since it's late at night, I'm going to sleep now
Good morning
We were able to sleep comfortably last night thanks to the air conditioner
I'm going to start the day by preparing breakfast for Ryua this morning as well
But Ryua doesn't seem to have any intention of eating breakfast
I'm sleepy this morning, too, so I'm going to drink a cup of tea and wake up
I think Ryua chose to sleep this morning
I need to get ready to eat breakfast while RYUA is sleeping
(Hambak steak)
(Egg)
(Rice)
(Buldak stir-fried noodles)
This morning, I prepared a simple but delicious combination
This combination is sometimes greasy
(Chonggak kimchi / Young radish kimchi)
When it's greasy, it's perfect to finish with kimchi
There's no need for words for Buldak stir-fried noodles
It is delicious
I enjoyed this simple and delicious breakfast
Thank you for watching until now
Bye!